Guide to the George Starkovich Ephemera Collection
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- George Starkovich collection of sociopolitical pamphlets and papers, 1935-1957; 0305-001; 4.44 cubic feet 23 boxes
  - Pamphlets and Small Publications, Series 2
    - Vatican Policy in the Second World War; L. H. Lehman; Agora Publishing Co., June, 1946 (Box 16)
    - We Can Have Homes; The Progressive Party Housing Program, Undated (Box 16)
    - The Races of Mankind; Ruth Benedict and Gene Weltfish; Public Affairs Committee, April, 1946 (Box 16)
    - Questions on Disarmament and Your Job; Friends Committee on National Legislation, Undated (Box 16)
    - Let's Join the Human Race; Stringfellow Barr; The University of Chicago Press, 1950 (Box 16)
    - The Wallace Plan: vs. the (Hoover) (Dulles) Marshall Plan; Henry A. Wallace; National Wallace for President Committee, Undated (Box 16)
    - The Case of Carl Marzani; Committee in Defense of Carl Marzani, Undated (Box 16)
    - Hey, Brother....There's a Law Against You!: An Analysis of the Mundt-Nixon Bill; The National Committee to Defeat the Mundt Bill, Undated (Box 16)
    - Hold High The Torch!; Richard O. Boyer; New Century Publishers, November, 1951 (Box 17)
    - Indicts: the Wall Street Conspirators; Eugene Dennis; the National Office, Communist Party, August, 1949 (Box 17)
    - The Case of Morton Sobell; D. N. Pritt; The National Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell in the Rosenberg Case, Undated (Box 17)
    - Jesus Haunts Me; Willard Uphaus, Undated (Box 17)
    - Common-Sense Welfare Is Everybody's Business: Put 178 On the Ballot; Citizens' Public Assistance Committee, Undated (Box 17)
    - The Nelson Case: State Sedition Laws are Weapons of Anti-Labor, Anti-Negro, Anti-Semitic Repression; Civil Rights Congress, May, 1955 (Box 17)
    - Argument to the Jury of Richard Gladstein in the New York Communist Trial; Richard Gladstein; Civil Rights Congress, Undated (Box 17)
    - The Fifth Amendment; Dean Erwin N. Griswold; Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, Undated (Box 17)
    - Wall Street's New Darling: Nazi Friend Ex-King Michael; Harry Fainaru; Romanian American Publishing Association Inc., Undated (Box 17)
    - The Melish Case: Challenge to the Church; The Melish Defense Committee, Undated (Box 17)
    - The Schneiderman Case: United States Supreme Court Opinion; American Committee For the Protection of Foreign Born, August, 1943 (Box 17)
    - The People and the Congress; William Z Foster; International Publishers, February, 1947 (Box 17)
    - This 4th of July; Milton Howard International Publishers, June, 1938 (Box 17)
    - The Centralia Case: A Joint Report on the Armistice Day Tragedy at Centralia, Washington, November 11, 1919; Brooklyn Eagle Press, November, 1930 (Box 17)
    - Bonus for Murder: Washington's Plot to Rearm Western Germany; Arthur D. Kahn; The Germain-American, May, 1951 (Box 17)
    - What Price Profits?; Max Weiss; New Century Publishers, April, 1947 (Box 17)
    - How's Your Health? The Fight for a National Health Program; Robert Friedman; New Century Publishers, February, 1947 (Box 17)
    - The MacArthur Ouster: A Letter to Members of the Communist Party; Eugene Dennis; Communist Party, USA, Undated (Box 17)
    - We Can Have Peace and Jobs!; Bernard Burton; New Century Publishers, May, 1953 (Box 17)
    - Verdict Against Freedom: Your Stake in the Communist Trial; Joseph North; New Century Publishers, November, 1949 (Box 17)
    - Indicts: the Wall Street Conspirators; Eugene Dennis; National Office Communist Party, August, 1948 (Box 17)
    - The Hour For Action Has Struck; International Publishers, June, 1942 (Box 17)
    - The People against the Trusts; Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, December, 1946 (Box 17)
    - How Wall Street Picks Your Pocket; George Morris; New Century Publishers, October, 1946 (Box 17)
    - The Federal Jury is Stacked Against You; Marion Bachrach; Communist Party Defense Committee, January, 1949 (Box 17)
    - To Secure Jewish Rights: The Communist Position; Alexander Bittelman; New Century Publishers, March, 1948 (Box 17)
    - Tax Relief for Whom-The Needy or the Greedy?: A Tax Program for 1947; Donald Freeman New Century Publishers, February, 1947 (Box 17)
    - Meat: A National Scandal; Lem Harris; New Century Publishers, November, 1946 (Box 17)
    - America's Housing Crisis; Louis Mitchell; New Century Publishers, May, 1946 (Box 17)
    - Who Owns America?; James S. Allen; New Century Publishers, June, 1946 (Box 17)
    - "Not Guilty!"; Claude Lightfoot; New Century Publishers, June, 1955 (Box 17)
    - A New Depression?; Bernard Burton; New Century Publishers, September, 1949 (Box 17)
    - Program for Survival: the Communist Position on the Jewish Question; Alexander Bittelman; New Century Publishers, January, 1947 (Box 17)
    - Verdict Against Freedom: Your Stake in the Communist Trial; Joseph North; New Century Publishers, November, 1955 (Box 18)
    - Because A Man Stood Up For Human Rights!; International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, Undated (Box 18)
    - What America Faces: The New War Danger and the Struggle for Peace, Democracy and Economic Security; Eugene Dennis; New Century Publishers, March, 1946 (Box 18)
    - The Constitution of the United States with the Amendments; International Publishers, 1942 (Box 18)
    - Questions & Answers: On the Piatakov-Radek Trial; William Z. Foster; International Publishers, March, 1937 (Box 18)
    - Publisher On Trial: A Symposium; The Committee to Defend Alexander Trachtenberg, 1952 (Box 18)
    - Dust Off Your Dreams: The story of American Youth for Democracy; American Youth For Democracy, December, 1945 (Box 18)
    - How Fare Youth?; Tom Dennison American Youth For Democracy, Undated (Box 18)
    - Elizabeth Gurley Flynn Speaks to the Court; Elizabeth Gurley Flynn; New Century Publishers, July, 1952 (Box 18)
    - American Intellectuals; Maxim Gorky; Union Labor, 1932 (Box 18)
    - Here's How We See It, Mr. Perkins; I. Taigin; New Century Publishers, December, 1946 (Box 18)
    - The American-Anglo-Soviet Alliance; The American Council on Soviet Relations, Undated (Box 18)
    - The Story of the Trenton Six; Elwood Dean; New Century Publishers, December, 1949 (Box 18)
    - The 3rd Party; Adam Lapin; The Daily People's World, Undated (Box 18)
    - Public Enemies in Public Office; Carl Hirsch; New Century Publishers, July, 1951 (Box 18)
    - For Your Children, Too, Undated (Box 18)
    - The Case of the Missing Helicopter or Youth Wants that Postwar World; Nathan Pearlman; American Youth For Democracy, Undated (Box 18)
    - Land without Capitalists; Dyson Carter; Progress Books, October, 1949 (Box 18)
    - Battle for America 1776-1861-1941; A. B. Magil; International Publishers, 1943 (Box 18)
    - Trends in American Capitalism: Profits and Living Standards; International Publishers, 1948 (Box 18)
    - Voices for Freedom; Civil Rights Congress, July, 1951 (Box 18)
    - If Inflation Comes; Joseph Gaer; CIO Political Action Committee, Undated (Box 18)
    - Gene Debs: The Story of a Fighting American; Herbert M. Morais & William Cahn; International Publishers, 1948 (Box 18)
    - Appeal; International Preparatory Commission for the International Conference in Defense of the Rights of Youth, 1952 (Box 18)
    - The Income 'Revolution'; Victor Perlo; International Publishers, 1945 (Box 18)
    - Gyps and Swindles; William Trufant Foster; Public Affairs Committee, 1945 (Box 18)
    - May Day 1947; Howard Fast; United May Day Committee, Undated (Box 18)
    - Tony Was Sentenced to Death!; Based on letters from Betty Bartlett, Edited by Anthony Simmons; United States Federation of Greek Maritime Unions, September, 1949 (Box 18)
    - The Everlasting Bridges Case; International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, May, 1955 (Box 18)
    - The Southern People's Common Program for Democracy, Prosperity and Peace Southern Regional Committee of the Communist Party, March, 1953 (Box 18)
    - Due Process in a Political Trial: The Record vs. The Press; National Nonpartisan Committee to Defend the Rights of the 12 Communist Leaders, Undated (Box 18)
    - The Double Edge of the Labor's Sword; Morris Hillquit, Samuel Gompers & Max J. Hayes; Socialist Party, National Office, Undated (Box 18)
    - The Case of Morton Sobell; D. N. Pritt; National Committee to Secure Justice For Morton Sobell in the Rosenberg Case, Undated (Box 18)
    - The Supreme Court on the Bridges Case; Justice Frank Murphy American Committee For the Protection of Foreign Born, August, 1945 (Box 19)
    - The Tenth Anniversary of American-Soviet Relations; National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Undated (Box 19)
    - Notes for Speakers who wish to Discuss Initiative 198; Washington Machinists Council, Undated (Box 19)
    - The Pavement Trail; United Automobile Workers of America, Undated (Box 19)
    - Register Christian Opinion! a Congressional Directory to Aid in Legislative Action in 1955; Board of World Peace of the Methodist Church, Undated (Box 19)
    - The Races of Mankind; Ruth Benedict & Gene Weltfish; Public Affairs Committee, April, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Political Economy Illustrated; James Erickson; James Erickson, Undated (Box 19)
    - Which Way for Young Americans?; Gus Hall; Challenge, October, 1950 (Box 19)
    - Without Fear or Favor; Glenn L. Archer; Protestants and Other Americans United for Separation of Church and State, Undated (Box 19)
    - In and Out of the Yoke: A Plain Story of the Farmer and the Nonpartisan League; Charles Edward Russell, Undated (Box 19)
    - Subversive Utterances: Anti-Wall Street--Anti-pope--Pro-Russian Propaganda, Undated (Box 19)
    - How to De-Control your Union of Communists; Rev. Charles Owen Rice; International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, Undated (Box 19)
    - Three Years 1944-1947; International Workers Order, June, 1947 (Box 19)
    - This Is My Husband; Esther Cooper Jackson; National Committee to Defend Negro Leadership, March, 1953 (Box 19)
    - It's Your Union They're After!; International Association of Machinists, Undated (Box 19)
    - Labor's Stake in the American-Soviet Friendship; addresses by William Green, R. J. Thomas, William Mcfetridge, Joseph Curran Etc.; National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Undated (Box 19)
    - Discrimination Against coloured People; Mary Yeates; W.F.T.U Publications, Undated (Box 19)
    - The Communist Position on The Negro Question; William Z. Foster, Benjamin J. Davis, Jr., Eugene Dennis, James E. Jackson, Etc.; New Century Publishers, February, 1947 (Box 19)
    - Women Who Work; Grace Hutchins; International Publishers, 1952 (Box 19)
    - Right-to-Work' Laws: Three Moral Studies; International Association of Machinists, 1955 (Box 19)
    - To Every Woman Everywhere, Undated (Box 19)
    - Montgomery, Alabama Money, Mississippi and Other Places; Eve Merriam; Cameron Associates, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Inside Job!; Herb Tank; New Century Publishers, May, 1947 (Box 19)
    - Lincoln's Third Party; Elizabeth Lawson; International Publishers, 1948 (Box 19)
    - The Negro in Hollywood Films; V. J. Jerome; Masses & Mainstream, Inc., December, 1950 (Box 19)
    - Woman Against Myth Betty Millard; International Publishers, 1948 (Box 19)
    - Negro Representation--A Step Towards Negro Freedom; Pettis Perry; New Century Publishers, March, 1952 (Box 19)
    - The Negro People in Struggle for Peace and Freedom; Benjamin J. Davis; New Century Publishers, February, 1951 (Box 19)
    - The Trucks Act: Michigan's Blueprint for a Fascist State; William Albertson; New Century Publishers, October, 1952 (Box 19)
    - Labor Unity: What AFL-CIO Merger Means for Workers; George Morris; New Century Publishers, March, 1955 (Box 19)
    - Heroines; Sasha Small; International Publishers, Undated (Box 20)
    - Women in the War; Elizabeth Gurley Flynn; International Publishers, November, 1942 (Box 20)
    - Mothers in Overalls; Eva Lapin; International Publishers, October, 1943 (Box 20)
    - A Southerner Looks at Negro Discrimination; selected writings of George W. Cable; International Publishers, 1946 (Box 20)
    - Behind the Florida Bombings: Who Killed NAACP Leader Harry T. Moore and His Wife; Joseph North; New Century Publishers, February, 1952 (Box 20)
    - Eyes on Washington!; Eric Burt; New Century Publishers, December, 1955 (Box 20)
    - The People Versus Segregated Schools; Doxey A. Wilkerson; New Century Publishers, February, 1955 (Box 20)
    - Marxism and Negro Liberation; Gus Hall; New Century Publishers, March, 1951 (Box 20)
    - Labor's Own William Z. Foster: A Communist's Fifty Years of Working class Leadership and Struggle; Elizabeth Gurley Flynn; New Century Publishers, March, 1949 (Box 20)
    - How to Write For Your Union Paper; Morris Watson & George Seldes; International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, August, 1943 (Box 20)
    - We Demand Freedom!; William L. Patterson; Civil Rights Congress, November, 1951 (Box 20)
    - A Tale of Two Waterfronts; George Morris Daily Worker, Undated (Box 20)
    - The Struggle for Negro Equality; John Saunders & Albert Parker; Pioneer Publishers, February, 1945 (Box 20)
    - Treacherous Passage; National Union Marine Cooks and Stewards, Undated (Box 20)
    - Report of the CIO Delegation To the Soviet Union; Submitted By James B. Carey; Congress of Industrial Organizations, Undated (Box 20)
    - Merchant Seamen and the Law; William L. Standard; National Maritime Union of America, December, 1945 (Box 20)
    - The Trotskyite 5th Column in the Labor Movement; New Century Publishers, January, 1945 (Box 20)
    - Testimony of John L. Lewis; Labor's Non-Partisan League, Undated (Box 20)
    - To Make Men Free; Webster Rogers, Undated (Box 20)
    - New Worlds for Women; Dorise Nielsen; Progress Publishing Co, 1945 (Box 20)
    - Smear and Run€¦; Citizens Committee to Preserve American Freedoms, Undated (Box 20)
    - The Case Against Waterfront Screening: Questions and Answers of Interest to Americans Committee Against Waterfront Screening, Undated (Box 20)
    - Labor and Anti-Semitism; George Morris ;New Century Publishers, May, 1953 (Box 20)
    - Behind the Lynching of Emmet Louis Till; Louis Burnham; Freedom Associates, Inc., 19694 (Box 20)
    - The Steel Workers and The Fight for Labor's Rights; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, June, 1952 (Box 20)
    - The C.I.O Today; George Morris; New Century Publishers, March, 1950 (Box 20)
    - The People Versus Segregated Schools; Doxy A. Wilkerson; New Century Publishers, February, 1955 (Box 20)
    - Forge Negro-Labor Unity for Peace and Jobs; Paul Robeson; Harlem Trade Union Council, August, 1950 (Box 20)
    - The Coal Miners and you; Elmer Felhaber; New Century Publishers, March, 1950 (Box 20)
    - UIBWM, Undated (Box 20)
    - How the Cradle of Liberty was Robbed; Joseph Morton; New Century Publishers, January, 1955 (Box 20)
    - Analysis of the Taft-Hartley Act; C.I.O Legal Department, August, 1947 (Box 20)
    - The "Crimes" of Claude Lightfoot and Junus Scales; Civil Rights Congress, Undated (Box 20)
    - Trade Unionism: The Road to Freedom; William Z. Foster; Chicago Labor News, Undated (Box 20)
    - Towards a Mass Communist Party! Every Party Member a Party Builder!; William Z. Foster; Communist Party, USA, Undated (Box 20)
    - The Way Out: A Program for American Labor; Introduction by M. J. Olgin; International Publishers, May, 1934 (Box 20)
    - Communists and the Trade Unions; Roy Hudson; International Publishers, October, 1943 (Box 20)
    - The Real Rickenbacker; Sender Garlin; International Publishers, April, 1943 (Box 20)
    - The Ingrams Shall Not Die!: Story of Georgia's New Terror; Harry Raymond; Daily Worker, March, 1948 (Box 20)
    - The Party of Negro and White; Pettis Perr; New Century Publishers, March, 1953 (Box 20)
    - A Letter to Congress: Defeat the Anti-Labor Smith Bill!; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, June, 1952 (Box 20)
    - The Steel Workers and The Fight for Labor's Rights; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, June, 1952 (Box 20)
    - Negro Workers After the War; National Negro Congress, April, 1945 (Box 20)
    - Agreement Between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (U.E.), Undated (Box 20)
    - Problems of Organized Labor Today; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, July, 1946 (Box 21)
    - William H. Sylvis and the National Labor Union; Charlotte Todes; International Publishers, 1942 (Box 21)
    - Labor and the Marshall Plan; William Z. Foster; International Publishers, March, 1948 (Box 21)
    - Organized Labor and the Fascist Danger€¦; William Z. Foster; International Publishers, August, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Communists and the Trade Unions; Roy Hudson; International Publishers, October, 1943 (Box 21)
    - Conspiracy to Strangle Labor; George Morris; International Publishers, 1951 (Box 21)
    - The Coal Miners: Their Problems in War and Peace; William Z. Foster; International Publishers, February, 1945 (Box 21)
    - Lynching and Frame-Up in Tennessee; Robert Minor; International Publishers, October, 1946 (Box 21)
    - The Negro People in the Struggle for Peace and Freedom; Benjamin J. Davis; International Publishers, February, 1941 (Box 21)
    - The Path of Negro Liberation; Benjamin J. Davis; International Publishers, April, 1947 (Box 21)
    - FEPC: How it was Betrayed, How it can be Saved; Robert Fowler Hall; International Publishers, February, 1950 (Box 21)
    - How the Cradle of Liberty was Robbed; Joseph Morton; International Publishers, January, 1945 (Box 21)
    - Women on Guard How the Women of the World Fight for Peace; Betty Millard; International Publishers, February, 1952 (Box 21)
    - The History of the Shorter Workday; Prepared by Labor Research Association; International Publishers, 1942 (Box 21)
    - Youth in Industry; Grace Hutchins; Union Labor, 1932 (Box 21)
    - The Slave Law; Lee Coe; The Daily People's World, Undated (Box 21)
    - Next Steps in the Struggle for Negro Freedom; Hugh Bradley; New Century Publishers, 1953 (Box 21)
    - To Stem this Tide: A Survey of Racial Tension Areas in the United States; Charles S. Johnson and Associates; The Pilgrim Press - Boston & Chicago, 1943 (Box 21)
    - The Ingrams; Harry Raymond & Mason Roberson; The Daily People's World, Undated (Box 21)
    - Maritime Workers at the Crossroads; Waterfront Sections, Communist Party. U.S.A., Undated (Box 21)
    - Freedom is Everybody's Job!; George W. Crockett, Jr.; National Nonpartisan Committee, Undated (Box 21)
    - An Introduction; Walter Hurt; Progress Publishing Co., Undated (Box 21)
    - Your Civil Rights: A Handbook for Trade Union Members and Organizers; Congress of Industrial Organizations, Undated (Box 21)
    - Labor's Stake in American-Soviet Friendship; William Green, R. J. Thomas, William Mcfettridge, Joseph Curran, Etc.; National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Undated (Box 21)
    - The Perfect Crime... Of Mr. Taft and Mr. Hartley; International Woodworkers of America CIO, Undated (Box 21)
    - The South's New Challenge; James E. Jackson; New Century Publishers, 1957 (Box 21)
    - Pettis Perry Speaks to the Court; New Century Publishers, 19176 (Box 21)
    - ...Smash The Chains Louis E. Burnham; American Youth For Democracy, Undated (Box 21)
    - Negro History: Its Lessons for our Time; Herbert Aptheker New Century Publishers, 1956 (Box 21)
    - You are on Trial; Marion Bachrach; New Century Publishers, January, 1949 (Box 21)
    - The Negro People on the March; Benjamin J. Davis; New Century Publishers, 1956 (Box 21)
    - Thaddeus Stevens: Militant Democrat and Fighter for Negro Rights; Elizabeth Lawson; International Publishers, 1942 (Box 21)
    - The Ilwu Story: Two Decades of Militant Unionism; International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, 1955 (Box 21)
    - The Cold War On American Labor; Henry Wallace; National Labor Committee for Wallace and Taylor, June, 1948 (Box 22)
    - The Taft-Hartley Plot Unfolds; California CIO Council, August, 1948 (Box 22)
    - Where is the CIO Going?; George Morris; New Century Publishers, March, 1949 (Box 22)
    - A Letter To Congress: Defeat the Anti-Labor Smith Bill!; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, June, 1952 (Box 22)
    - Not 12 Men on Trial...But Everybody!; Communist Party, USA, Undated (Box 22)
    - The Case of Claude Lightfoot; The Lightfoot Defense Committee, Undated (Box 22)
    - U.S. Labor Looks At Europe; American Committee to Survey Labor Conditions In Europe, 1951 (Box 22)
    - Bargaining for the Union...A discussion for IWA Job Stewards and Committeemen; International Woodworkers of America CIO, Undated (Box 22)
    - Parliamentary Procedure; International Woodworkers of America CIO, Undated (Box 22)
    - Agreement; Northwest Steel Rolling Mills, Inc, 1952 (Box 22)
    - Chug-Chug: A Children's Story for the Whole Family; The United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, CIO, September, 1947 (Box 22)
    - The Mystery of 1000 "Vanished" Ships; Al Lannon & Harry Mann; Waterfront Sections of the Communist Party, USA., Undated (Box 22)
    - Know... Your Union; International Woodworkers of America CIO, November, 1948 (Box 22)
    - The Negro People and the Soviet Union; Paul Robeson; New Century Publishers, January, 1950 (Box 22)
    - Constitution and By-Laws; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE), December, 1953 (Box 22)
    - For Freedom and Peace; Address by Paul Robeson; Council on African Affairs, June, 1949 (Box 22)
    - Problems of Organized Labor Today; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, July, 1946 (Box 22)
    - Lessons of the Inglewood Strike; William Z. Foster; New York State Communist Party, Undated (Box 22)
    - Washington and Lincoln: The American Tradition; Joseph North; International Publishers, February, 1942 (Box 22)
    - Shop Paper Manual: A Handbook for Comrades Active in Shop Paperwork; International Publishers, December, 1930 (Box 22)
    - McCarthyism in the Courts: the Story of Steve Nelson Frame-Up; Mel Fiske; Provisional Committee to Free Steve Nelson, 1953 (Box 22)
    - The Forced Labour Swindle; William Wainwright; British-Soviet Society, October, 1949 (Box 22)
    - The Un-Americanism of the Hearst's John Sentinel; Eugene Dennis; The Communist Party of Wisconsin, Undated (Box 22)
    - Stop McCarthy Now!; Leon Wofsy; Labor Youth League, March, 1954 (Box 22)
    - Ideas Behind Bars?; Len Goldsmith Civil Rights Congress, Undated (Box 22)
    - The Congressional Inquisition; Corliss Lamont; Basic Pamphlets, May, 1954 (Box 22)
    - Workers, Defend Your Unions!; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, January, 1947 (Box 22)
    - The Rankin Witch Hunt; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, December, 1945 (Box 22)
    - "I Challenge the Un-Americans"; Eugene Dennis; Communist Party, USA, May, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Cold War in the Classroom; Samuel Sillen; Masses & Mainstream, Inc., April, 1950 (Box 22)
    - Red Tape and Barbed Wire; Sender Garlin; Civil Rights Congress, 1952 (Box 22)
    - Police State Terror; Abner Green; New Century Publishers, 1953 (Box 22)
    - Labor and the War; William Z. Foster; International Publishers, January, 1942 (Box 22)
    - The Strike Situation and Organized Labor's Wage and Job Strategy; William Z. Foster; New Century Publishers, November, 1945 (Box 22)
    - What is McCarthyism...; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE), Undated (Box 22)
    - The "Save the Country" Racket; John L. Spivak; New Century Publishers, November, 1948 (Box 22)
    - Voices for Freedom #2; Civil Rights Congress, October, 1951 (Box 22)